bioskops25.com 2014-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Bioskops25.com

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, Cinemaindo Media a.k http://cinemaindo.net have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, Cinemaindo Media will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * Cinemaindo Media will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * Cinemaindo Media will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * Cinemaindo Media will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * Cinemaindo Media will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * Cinemaindo Media will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

Cinemaindo Media are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
